const Parliament = [
	{
		questionText: 'Article 79 ',
		ans: ['Article 79 : Constitution of Parliament'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 80 ',
		ans: ['Composition of the Council of States'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 81',
		ans: ['Composition of the House of the People'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 82',
		ans: ['Readjustment after each census'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 83',
		ans: ['Duration of Houses of Parliament'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 84',
		ans: ['Qualification for membership of Parliament'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 85',
		ans: ['Sessions of Parliament, prorogation and dissolution'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 86',
		ans: [' Right of President to address and send messages to Houses'],
	},
	{
		questionText: ' Article 87',
		ans: ['Special address by the President'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Article 88 ',
		ans: ['Rights of Ministers and Attorney-General as respects Houses'],
	},
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
	// {
	// 	questionText: '',
	// 	ans: [''],
	// },
];

export default Parliament;
